getmytime.com 2013-06-09

# Web Based Time Management QuickBooks® Timer, GetMyTime.com _ Privacy Statement

   Privacy Statement

As an Internet user, you no doubt recognize the usefulness of this amazing medium. A medium of such great promise in one-to-one and one-to-many communications does not come without its concerns. Many members of the on-line community are rightfully concerned about maintaining a comfortable level of privacy. As active members of the on-line community, **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** supports industry self-regulation. We believe all web sites should openly share their policies and practices of collecting and processing information. 

**Forms**

We use web-based forms to collect vital information from parties interested in communicating with **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com**. We ask that users share as much information as deemed appropriate. This information is used for the sole purpose of serving our clients better. We will not sell, share or rent this information to any outside parties unless you have so requested. Your company information is encrypted while being uploaded to **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** using a Thawte SSL Encryption License. 

**Billing Information**

We request billing information from the user on our order page. Here a user must provide contact information (i.e. name and shipping address) and financial information (i.e. credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. All billing information is encrypted during transit to and from our servers (using a Thawte SSL Encryption License), and while being stored. 

**Cookies**

In many cases cookies are greatly misunderstood. When used as intended, a cookie is simply a reminder that some web sites place on your hard drive. This allows the web site in question to recognize your computer on return visits. For example, in order to view the New York Times web site, you must first register with their service. After registration, a cookie is placed on the user's machine so the web site will recognize their web browser the next time they return and will not prompt them to register again. Most standard browsers have the option of refusing all cookies \- so no web site can force a cookie upon you if you do not want it. **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** uses cookies to track your "session" or visit to our web site. This allows us to enhance your visit to the web site, and evaluate overall usage of **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** site. 

**Server Activity**

Server software employed by all Internet Service Providers, is capable of detecting: 

  * The browser name and version you are using (i.e. Netscape 3.1) 
  * The types of plug-ins you are using (i.e. Flash, Shockwave, Real Audio) 
  * Your operating system (i.e. Windows 2000, MacOS, Windows NT). 
  * IP number. - IP Addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

This information is helpful in delivering the appropriate content to you, the end user. For example, if our software detects that you are using the Flash plug-in, you might view a much higher quality and faster-loading animation than a user without the plug-in. This information is not stored or tracked and is only used to provide you with better information. The following information can NOT be gathered from you unless you willingly submit it: 

  * Your e-mail address. 
  * Your credit card number. 
  * Your street address or phone number. 

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that **GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When any of our web forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. 

While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. As policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your e-mail address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done by contacting [Customer Support](mailto:customerservice@getmytime.com). 

**Advertising**

**GetMyTime.com/GetMyExpense.com** advertises on Google Adwords. Part of the Google technology allows us to know how many people found our site through Google Adwords and eventually signed up for the free trial. It does not tell us WHICH customers found us through Google.

|| Back to top
